Wilton Historical Society Wilton Historical Information Collection
Wilton History Room, Wilton Historical Society
- 3. Miscellaneous (by topic)
  - Government and services
    - Housing - Senior citizens, undated; See also Ogden House, Pilgrim Housing. (Cabinet 4, Folder 319d)
    - Hurlbutt Street Post Office, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 463)
    - Marhoffer Fire Station, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 282)
    - Moderate Income Housing Report, 1985 (Cabinet 4, Folder 319c)
    - Old Age Assistance Tax, 1939-1942 (Cabinet 4, Folder 500b, 500c, 500d, 500e)
    - Pilgrim Housing - Housing types and site plans, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 451a)
    - Pilgrim Housing - Legal arguments, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 451b)
    - Pilgrim Housing - Maps and site plans, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 452a)
    - Pilgrim Housing - Meeting minutes and correspondence, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 452b)
    - Pilgrim Housing - Planning and Zoning Commission, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 453a)
    - Pilgrim Housing - Traffic Engineering Evaluation, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 453b)
    - Police Department, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 454)
    - Poorhouse, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 458)
    - Post Office building, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 467)
    - Post offices - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 460a)
    - Post rider, 1673 (Cabinet 4, Folder 466)
    - Postal system, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 468)
    - Report on Multi-Family Housing, 1969; This is a League of Women Voters report. (Cabinet 4, Folder 319b)
    - Republicans, undated; See also MAN, Isabel Rock. (Cabinet 4, Folder 457)
    - Reservoirs, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 472c)
    - Senior citizens, senior center, and nursing homes, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 480)
    - Sewer Authority, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 481)
    - Solid Waste Management in Wilton, 1973; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 488)
    - Surveys, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 495)
    - Telephone, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 552a)
    - Telephone service, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 504)
    - Town Hall, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 522)
    - Town of Wilton - Charter, 1968-1969 (Cabinet 4, Folder 291ba)
    - Town of Wilton - Charter - Committee minutes, 1962-1992 (Cabinet 4, Folder 291b)
    - Town of Wilton - Charter - General information, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 291a)
    - Town of Wilton - Charter - Newspaper articles, 1961-1962 (Cabinet 4, Folder 291c)
    - Town of Wilton - Communication between Local Boards and Citizens, 1987; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 294)
    - Town of Wilton - Election brochures, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 292a)
    - Town of Wilton - Finance Board, 1915 (Cabinet 4, Folder 292b)
    - Town of Wilton - Fiscal Study Committee, 1957-1960 (Cabinet 4, Folder 293a)
    - Town of Wilton - Local Government, 1957-1958; File 193b covers the years 1957-1958. File 293c covers the years 1959-1960. (Cabinet 4, Folder 293b, 293c)
    - Town of Wilton - Officers and meetings, 1726-1899, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 295)
    - Town of Wilton - Ordinances, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 296a)
    - Town of Wilton - Property Evaluation, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 523)
    - Town of Wilton - Selectmen, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 296b)
    - Town of Wilton - State of the Town Report, 2008 (Cabinet 4, Folder 296bb)
    - Town of Wilton - Study of local Government, 2002 (Cabinet 4, Folder 296c)
    - Town of Wilton - Tax Study Report, 1947; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 297c)
    - Town of Wilton - Taxable property list, 1864; The list covers names from Morehouse through Nash. (Cabinet 4, Folder 297a)
    - Town of Wilton - Taxes and early assessment lists, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 297b)
    - Town of Wilton - Town Clerk, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 298a)
    - Town of Wilton - Town Fiscal Study Committee Report, 1959 (Cabinet 4, Folder 298b)
    - Town of Wilton - Town Government, 1961-1995 (Cabinet 4, Folder 298c)
    - Town of Wilton - Town Meeting, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 298d)
    - Town of Wilton - Voter lists and elections, 1802-1959; Lists cover the years 1802-1865, 1898, and 1959. See MAP N-7 for list of electors. (Cabinet 4, Folder 299)
    - Town of Wilton - Voters Guide, undated; This is a League of Women Voters document. (Cabinet 4, Folder 300)
    - Tree Art Exhibition - Committee planning, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549ea)
    - Tree Art Exhibition - Exhibitors, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549eb)
    - Tree Art Exhibition - Publicity, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549ec)
    - Tree Plans, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 550)
    - Volunteer Fire Department, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 285)
    - Water in Wilton, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 677a)
    - Wilton - World wide web home page, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 758)
    - Wilton officials, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 752)
    - Wilton property taxes, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 501)
    - Wilton residents list, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 753aa)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Adaptive Use, undated; See also WHS, Lambert Corners. (Cabinet 4, Folder 526aa)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Center School Design Competition, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 526b)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Center School Plan, 1983 (Cabinet 4, Folder 527a)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Comprehensive Plan, 1967 (Cabinet 4, Folder 527b)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Inventory of town owned properties, 1975 (Cabinet 4, Folder 528a)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Landfill, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 528b)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 526a)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Plan of Development, Amendments, 1987 (Cabinet 4, Folder 528c)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Planning in Wilton Profile, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 529b)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Planning in Wilton Study, 1974; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 529a)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Questionnaire, 1985 (Cabinet 4, Folder 529c)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Study of Town Owned Properties, 1975; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 531a)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Suburbia, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 531b)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Town Plan of Development, 1963 (Cabinet 4, Folder 532)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Town Records, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 537a)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Trails, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 537b)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Wilton Center Area Plan, 1969 (Cabinet 4, Folder 535)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Wilton Center planning, 1946; Contains a blueprint. (Cabinet 4, Folder 534)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Wilton Center Study, 1975 (Cabinet 4, Folder 536a)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Wilton: A Report on Problems and Objectives, 1954 (Cabinet 4, Folder 533)
    - Wilton Town Planning - Your Town, 1951 (Cabinet 4, Folder 536b)
    - Wilton: A Study of Its Town Government, 1958-1961 (Cabinet 4, Folder 303)
    - Wilton's Government Present and Future, 1971 (Cabinet 4, Folder 304)
    - Zoning - Lynch v. Zoning Board, 1950 (Cabinet 5, Folder 790)
    - Zoning - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 780)
    - Zoning- Furniture factory, 1945-1946 (Cabinet 5, Folder 785)
  - Historic districts, landmarks, and neighborhoods
    - Boundary rock, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 133bb)
    - Branchville, undated; See also WHI, Transportation. (Cabinet 4, Folder 133c)
    - Cannon Crossing, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 138c)
    - Cannondale, undated; See also NEI. For Cannondale: A Connecticut Neighborhood, see WHS Files, "Publications." (Cabinet 4, Folder 138a)
    - Cannondale-Zion Hill National Historic District, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 317d)
    - Georgetown - Development, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 289c)
    - Georgetown - History, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 289a)
    - Georgetown - National Register of Historic Places Inventory and Information, 1986-1987 (Cabinet 4, Folder 289b)
    - Georgetown National Historic District, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 317b)
    - Historic districts - Bald Hill proposal, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bha)
    - Historic districts - Cannondale neighborhood - Correspondence, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bib)
    - Historic districts - Draft report on Hurlbutt Street, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bf)
    - Historic districts - Draft report on Schlichting house, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bg)
    - Historic districts - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316a)
    - Historic districts - Report on Ambler Farm, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bh)
    - Historic districts - Report on Cannondale neighborhood, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bia)
    - Historic districts - Report on Georgetown neighborhood, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316be, 216bea)
    - Historic districts - Report on Hurlbutt Street Schoolhouse, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bc)
    - Historic districts - Report on Lambert Corners, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316ba)
    - Historic districts - Report on Old Town Hall, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bb)
    - Historic districts - Study Committee, 1962-1963 (Cabinet 4, Folder 316aa)
    - Historic districts - Wilton Historical Society Museum Complex, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 316bd)
    - Historic houses - Miscellaneous, undated; See also Book 728.37097469 by Carboni. (Cabinet 4, Folder 318a)
    - Hurlbutt Street School National Historic District, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 317g)
    - J. Alden Weir Farm National Historic District, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 317c)
    - Lambert House National Historic District, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 317f)
    - “Living in Georgetown,” New York Times, 2005 (Cabinet 4, Folder 289aa)
    - National Historic Districts - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 317a)
    - Restoration of Buildings, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 473)
    - Silvermine Center National Historic District, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 317h)
    - Silvermine District - History, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 483)
    - Wilton Center, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 687a)
    - Wilton Center Building, undated; Includes notes by G. Evans Hubbard. (Cabinet 5, Folder 687b)
    - Wilton Center Development, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 687c)
    - Wilton Center National Historic District, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 317e)
    - Wilton Commons, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 687d)
    - Wilton Community Forum Day, 1980 (Cabinet 5, Folder 688)
    - Wilton Forum, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 700)
  - Miscellaneous
    - "A Brief View of Methods Available to the Community for the Acquisition of Open Space", 1971; This is a League of Women Voters report. (Cabinet 4, Folder 228b)
    - Abolition Movement, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 100)
    - Alcohol - "Wet vs. Dry" issue, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 682)
    - Alcohol - Miscellaneous, undated; See also WHI, "Wet vs. Dry" issue. See also MAN, Wilton Temperance Society. (Cabinet 4, Folder 102bb)
    - Archaeology, undated; See also WHI, Recreation, Allen’s Meadow, and "Archaeological Survey of Wilton" in Books 974.69 Newhouse. (Cabinet 4, Folder 102c)
    - Charter Oak, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549a)
    - Conservation - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 228a)
    - Constitution Oak, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549b)
    - Dinosaurs, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 230b)
    - Division of the Proprietors of Norwalk, 1738-1745 (Cabinet 4, Folder 233e)
    - Economic depression of the 1750s, undated; Contents also relate to the French and Indian Wars. (Cabinet 4, Folder 230a)
    - Geography and Geology of Wilton, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 288a)
    - Geology, Hydrology and Archeology of Wilton, undated; See also Map Tube #9. (Cabinet 4, Folder 288b)
    - Go Green Festival, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 228c)
    - Herbarium - File list, undated; This is the file list for Anna Carpenter's herbarium. See also WGC, CARD FILE drawers. (Cabinet 4, Folder 310)
    - Hospitals, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 319ac)
    - Ice cutting, harvesting, and houses, undated; See also OH tape #43. (Cabinet 4, Folder 319f)
    - List of Plants of Wilton, 1896-1926; Notes on scientific name, location found, and growing conditions of plants in Wilton, compiled by Anna E. Carpenter. It is stored in a card catalog drawer, sitting on the shelf with the Wilton Garden Club herbarium collection. (Cabinet 26)
    - List of Professionals in Wilton, circa 1905; List compiled by G. Evans Hubbard. It is an alphabetical file of Wilton residents who were doctors, ministers, teachers, lawyers, senators, etc., during the years 1726-1905. (Cabinet 27, Folder 2:9)
    - List of Wilton names, undated; Alphabetic file of names found on deeds, contracts, in ledgers, Bible records, receipts, etc., with some notations. (Cabinet 27, Folder 2:6)
    - Medical personnel, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 305)
    - Meeting House Oak, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549cb)
    - Methodism - David Hermon Van Hoosear and Francis Asbury, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 472b)
    - Migrations - Gold Rush correspondence, undated; See also WHI, Ballston, New York. (Cabinet 4, Folder 367)
    - Migrations - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 365)
    - Miscellaneous writings, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 400)
    - Money, 1740-1848 (Cabinet 4, Folder 410a)
    - Mulberry trees, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549d)
    - Natural phenomena, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 414)
    - Newspapers - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 420a)
    - Norwalk Gazette indexing, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 420b)
    - Norwalk pottery, 1954-1984 (Cabinet 4, Folder 470a)
    - Notable Wilton trees, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549e)
    - Nuclear Freeze Committee - Legal matters, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 421a)
    - Nuclear Freeze Committee - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 421b)
    - Nursing and Home Care, undated; See also OH, tape 45. (Cabinet 4, Folder 422)
    - Oblong, New York, v. Oblong, Connecticut, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 423b)
    - Ornithology, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 425d)
    - Public health, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 307)
    - Recipes and receipts, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470ab)
    - Recycling in Wilton, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 471a)
    - Refugees, 1975 (Cabinet 4, Folder 471b)
    - Religion - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 472a)
    - Slavery, undated; See also file on Comstock, Cesar, 1709-1773. (Cabinet 4, Folder 485)
    - Slaves - Notes by David Hermon Van Hoosear, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 486b)
    - Slaves - Notes on slaves in Wilton by Helen Gregory, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 486a)
    - Smallpox, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 487b)
    - Underground Railroad, undated; See also MAP TUBE #4. (Cabinet 4, Folder 487a)
    - Weather, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 677b)
    - Wilton History Room - Donations, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 318c)
    - Wilton History Room - Expansion, 1995 (Cabinet 4, Folder 318b)
    - Wilton History Room - Information and register, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 318ab)
    - Wilton Library, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 750, 751)
    - Wilton poems, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 753a)
    - Wilton Town Historian, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 314)
    - Wilton trees - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 549ca)
    - Wilton, England, 1942-1973; See also OH, tape 30 (Cabinet 5, Folder 690, 691a, 691b, 692, 693)
    - Witches and witchcraft, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 760)
    - Works Progress Administration murals and general information, undated; See also PHO. (Cabinet 5, Folder 770)
  - Open spaces, parks, and trails
    - Allen’s Meadow, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470ac)
    - Ambler Farm, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 426aa)
    - Bicycle trails, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 470b)
    - Bradley Park (Belden Hill Park), undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 426b)
    - Cherry Lane Park, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 426c)
    - Horseshoe Park, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 426d)
    - Kent Park, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 426e)
    - Linear Park, undated; See also WHI, Transportation, River Walk. (Cabinet 4, Folder 426f)
    - Merwin Meadows, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427a)
    - Mini-Park Study, 1974 (Cabinet 4, Folder 427b)
    - Open spaces - Miscellaneous, 1966-1968; File 425ba covers the years 1966-1968 and includes map of local trails and villages. File 425bb covers the years 1971-1998. File 425bc covers the year 1999. File 425bd covers the years 2000 through the present. (Cabinet 4, Folder 425ba, 425bb, 425bc, 425bd)
    - Parks - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 426a)
    - Quarry Head - Brochures and maps, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427ca)
    - Quarry Head - Correspondence and reports, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427cb)
    - Quarry Head - Demolition and management, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427cc)
    - Quarry Head - History, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427cd)
    - Quarry Head - Legal documents, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427cda)
    - Quarry Head - Newspaper articles, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427ce)
    - Quarry Head - Openings, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427cf)
    - Quarry Head - Photos, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427cg)
    - Schenck's Island, undated; See also WLCT. (Cabinet 4, Folder 427d)
    - Town Forest, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427e)
    - Town Forest maps, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 427f)
    - Town of Wilton parks, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 428)
    - Wilton Community Park (Kiwanis), undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 429a)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Activities, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754a)
    - Wilton Trails Association - By-Laws and Consent of the Incorporations, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754b)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Certificate of the Incorporation, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754c)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Correspondence received, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754e)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Correspondence sent, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754d)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Correspondence with landowners, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754f)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Dissolution, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754q)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Founding and chart, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754p)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Insurance, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754i)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Internal Revenue Service exemption application and Employee Identification Number, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754g)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Membership letters, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754j)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Membership lists, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754k)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Minutes and agendas, 1970-1980, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754l)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Minutes and agendas, 1981-1996, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754m)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Newsletters, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754n)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Newspaper clippings, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754o)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Trail maps, undated; See also MC. (Cabinet 5, Folder 754s)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Trails organizational information, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754r)
    - Wilton Trails Association - Treasurer’s reports, undated (Cabinet 5, Folder 754h)
    - Woodcock Nature Center, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 429b)
  - Roads and transportation
    See also NEI, Road Names, and Book 974.69 Sturges.
    - "Bridge to Nowhere", undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 134b)
    - Branchville Railroad Station - "Railroad Tenement to Victorian Rooming House", 1852-1880; See also PHO. (Cabinet 4, Folder 546c)
    - Branchville Railroad Station - National Register, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 546ca)
    - Branchville Railroad Station - Newspaper articles, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 546cb)
    - Branchville Railroad Station - Report, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 546cc)
    - Branchville Railroad Station - Research, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 546cd)
    - Bridge - Route 33 and Route 7, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 135)
    - Bridges - Miscellaneous, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 134a)
    - Cannondale Railroad Station, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 546b)
    - Citizens for a Balanced Environment (CBET), undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 538a)
    - Coaching Days, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 538b)
    - Commuters, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 538c)
    - Danbury and Norwalk Railroad, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 539)
    - History of Wilton roads, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 474a)
    - Hitching posts, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 319a)
    - Merritt Parkway, 1990- (Cabinet 4, Folder 474c)
    - Merritt Parkway, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 540b)
    - Milestones, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 370)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford Railroad, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 540c)
    - Railroad bridge replacement, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 136)
    - Railroad fares and schedules, 1891-1978; Contents are from 1891, 1958-1960, and 1978. (Cabinet 4, Folder 542)
    - Railroad history, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 543)
    - Roads and transportation - History, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 540a)
    - Route 7 - "The Road North", undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 477bd)
    - Route 7 - History, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 547a)
    - Route 7 - Miscellaneous, 1939-1988; File 476b covers the years 1939-1969. File 476c covers the years 1970-1979. File 477a begins coverage from 1988. (Cabinet 4, Folder 475, 476a, 476b, 477a)
    - Route 7 - Newspaper articles and letters, 1970-1989; File 477ba covers the years 1970-1971. File 477bb covers 1972. File 477bc covers the years 1980-1989. (Cabinet 4, Folder 477ba, 477bb, 477bc)
    - Route 7 - Safety: Report of Public Safety, 1985 (Cabinet 4, Folder 478)
    - Route 7- Relocation maps, 1963 (Cabinet 4, Folder 547d)
    - Route 7 Study, 1987; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 547c)
    - Route 7 Study, 1970; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 547b)
    - Scenic roads, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 474d)
    - South Wilton / Kent Railroad Station, 1962-1978; Contents are from 1962, 1974, and 1978. (Cabinet 4, Folder 546a)
    - Steamship, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 548a)
    - Transportation Safety - School transportation, 1975 (Cabinet 4, Folder 548b)
    - Whitton, Lindsey - "Wilton Roads", 1994 (Cabinet 4, Folder 474b)
    - Wilton Railroad Station, 1841-1957 (Cabinet 4, Folder 544)
  - Schools
    - A Better Chance (ABC) School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 234b)
    - Bald Hill School District, undated; See also Ledger 124, MC 7, and SC. (Cabinet 4, Folder 235)
    - Belden Hill School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 236)
    - Board of Education, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 237)
    - Cannondale School, undated; See also Book 372.97469 (copy). (Cabinet 4, Folder 239)
    - Center School, 1929-1984 (Cabinet 4, Folder 240b)
    - Center School Property conversion, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 241b)
    - Center School Study, 1980-1981; This is a League of Women Voters study. (Cabinet 4, Folder 241a)
    - Center School, original schoolhouse, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 240a)
    - Chestnut Hill School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 242a)
    - Cider Mill School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 242b)
    - Community Nursery School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 243a)
    - Comstock School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 243b)
    - Cooperative School, 1946 (Cabinet 4, Folder 244)
    - Driscoll School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 245)
    - Essay contest, 1957 (Cabinet 4, Folder 246)
    - Georgetown's First Schools, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 247a)
    - Gilbert & Bennett School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 247b)
    - Hillside School, Norwalk, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 247c)
    - Histories and reminiscences, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 248a)
    - Hurlbutt Street School, undated; See also HSSH and Book 372.97469 by Nancy Cole. (Cabinet 4, Folder 248b)
    - Kent District School, undated (Cabinet 4, Folder 250a)
    - Kent School Record of the Proceedings, 1933-1880 (Cabinet 4, Folder 250b)
    - Know Your Schools, 1982; This is a League of Women Voters report. (Cabinet 4, Folder 251)
    - Lockwood Academy (Brown Preparatory School), 1851 (Cabinet 4, Folder 252a)